(忆往昔)
天使们该做点事儿了啊  对吧
Angels got to have something to do, right,
我们现在可是后天启时期
Now that we're post-apocalypse?
拉斐尔和他的追随者们
Raphael and his followers,
他们想要他掌管天堂
they want him to rule heaven.
我  和大多数其他天使
I -- and many others --
最怕的就是让他接手
The last thing we want is to let him take over.
你是说内战
You're talking civil war.
巴尔萨泽
Balthazar.
很高兴见到你
It's so good to see you.
你偷了摩西之杖
You stole the staff of moses.
我偷的东西多了去了
I stole a lot of things.
-我需要武器  -这个不行
- I need the weapons. - Don't ask that.
如果能打败拉斐尔  就可以结束这一切
If we can beat Raphael, we can end this!
告诉拉斐尔
Tell, uh, Raphael...
死远点吧
...to bite me.
不
No.
直到下次和他见面
Until next time.
我要和人通话
I've got to make a call.
你可以用我的电话
I got a cell you can use.
不是那种通话
It's not that kind of call.
是的  父亲
Yes, father.
露比
Ruby?
Ruby!
很高兴再见到你  迪恩
Good to see you again, dean.
她是个恶魔  萨姆  没啥好说的
She's a demon, Sam, period.
他们想杀了我们  我们也想杀了他们
They want us dead. We want them dead.
看她对你做了什么  她是毒药  萨姆
Look what she did to you! She's poison, Sam!
(如今)
鲍比哪去了
Where's bobby?
在城里  补充补给呢
In town, supply run.
就这鬼天气
In this?
是啊  他是纯爷们儿
Yeah, man's a hero.
东西也确实都用光了
We were officially out of hunter's helper.
好啊  孩子们
Hello, boys.
你们看过"教父"吧
You've seen "The Godfather," right?
巴尔萨泽
Balthazar...
在结尾  迈克尔·科里昂
You know, the end, where Michael Corleone
派他的手下去解决掉他的敌人
sends his men to kill his enemies
干净利落一举全灭
in one big, bloody swoop?
嗨
Hey!
死海盐  不错  不错
"Dead sea brine." Good, good, good.
你知道  莫·格林眼睛中弹
You know, Moe Greene gets it in the eye,
然后唐·库在旋转门中弹
and Don Cuneo gets it in the revolving door?
我说了  嗨
I said "Hey."
是的
You did.
说了两次
Twice.
真不错
Good for you.
羊羔的血  羊羔的血
Blood of lamb. Blood of lamb.
啤酒  凉披萨
Beer, cold pizza.
羊羔的血  好的
blood of lamb. Yes!
羊羔的血
Blood of lamb!
你扯什么教父
Why are you talking about "The Godfather"?
因为我们简直是身临其境  现在  就今晚
Because we're in it -- right now, tonight.
而扮演迈克尔·科里昂的正是
And in the role of Michael Corleone --
大天使拉斐尔
The archangel Raphael.
能给我们解释一下吗
You mind telling us what you mean?
不  不  不
No, no, no, no.
好的
Yes.
圣徒之骨
Bone of a lesser saint.
这段椎骨非常合适
This vertebra will do very nicely.
你们辛格先生有用的东西真不少
Your Mr. Singer does keep a beautiful pantry.
等等  拉斐尔在追杀你
Wait, Raphael is after you?
拉斐尔在追杀我们所有人
Raphael is after us all.
他加强了自己的力量
You see, he's consolidated his strength.
现在已经开始行动了
And now he's on the move.
-小卡呢  -小卡啊
- And where's cass? - Oh, Cassie?
他深处地下呢
He is deep, deep underground.
我们的老好人斐斐出了张猎杀名单
So, good old Raffy put out a hit list
囊括了所有帮助过我们萌卡的好人们
on every last samaritan who helped our dear Cass --
你们也在其中
Including both of you.
更重要的是  还有我
And so much more importantly, me.
他想把小卡引出来
See, he wants to draw Cass out in the open.
你觉得我们会信你吗
And you expect us to just believe you?
那别信
Oh, don't.
反正我把你们扔哪你们就得去哪
You'll go where I throw you either way.
你这什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
时间到了  先生们
That's all the time we have, gentlemen.
在哪呢
Where is it?
怎么了
What happened there?
超炫的  我知道
Oh. Garish, I know.
你斐叔派了他最恶毒的手下来对付我
You see, uncle Raffy sent one of his nastiest to handle me.
我很受宠若惊
I'm flattered, actually.
我其中一个肺也挂了
And down a lung at the moment,
不过没啥关系
but that's all right.
这个是给你的
Oh, here's for you.
-我拿这玩意干嘛  -带着跑
- What am I supposed to do with this? - Run with it.
维吉尔
Virgil!
我说了  跑
I said, run!
停
Cut!
落地相当不错  干得好
Real good solid fall. Way to go.
杰瑞德  詹森  太棒了
Jared, jensen! Outstanding!
真是太好了
That was just great.
凶鬼恶灵  第1场重复  第1次拍摄
"Supernatural," Scene one echo, take one.
打板  标记
Tail slate. Marker!
[邪恶力量 第6季第15集]
没有天使
So...No angels?
大概  没天使
No angels, I think.
但那很棒啊
But that was great!
不是特技的问题
It's not a problem with the stunt.
是  信号的问题
It's a problem with the...signal.
我们是不是要杀掉什么人
Should we be killing anybody?
有干扰
Interference.
-我想不用  -我们能用多少
- I don't think so. - Well, how much did we get?
-跑吗  -大概一半
- Running? - About half.
-往哪跑  -我们倒退到
- Where? - Gets us right up to where they --
倒退到他们撞上窗户之前
just before they hit the window.
他们撞上窗户的部分
You know, the part where they hit the window
可是段好戏
was the good part.
我们可以清理下  重置窗户
Well, we can clean up, reset the window,
基本上  需要95分钟
takes about 95 minutes, basically.
所以我们需要洗掉
So, we'd have to blow off the scene
他们坐在黑斑羚上谈心的那场戏
where they sit on the impala and talk about their feelings.
那好
Ha. Right.
那你来回吐槽信
You answer the hate mail.
或者我们可以让他们飞向窗户
Or we could have them fly at the window,
然后暂停
then freeze frame.
切黑屏  继续演
Then cut to black, act out.
暂停
Freeze frame.
是啊
Um...Yeah.
暂停
Freeze frame.
可以试试
Serviceable.
好吧
Fine.
随便
Whatever.
第六季
Season six.
下一场
Moving on.
Moving on!
杰瑞德和詹森收工
That's a wrap on Jared and Jensen!
谁是
W-who the hell are --
杰瑞德  三分钟  好吗
Jared! Three minutes, okay? Great.
我们去哪
Where are we going?
詹森  你在这
Jensen, there you are!
坐到椅子上
Let's just get you in the chair.
椅子
"Chair"?
好的  亲
Okay, hon,
咱们来把妆卸掉
We're just gonna get this makeup off your face.
我没化什么...
I'm not wearing any ma--
哦  天
Oh, crap!
我是个花哨的娘炮
I'm a painted whore!
我是崔西·伊云
Trish Evian here
这位是凶鬼恶灵中的杰瑞德·帕德里克
with Jared Padalecki from tv's "Supernatural."
杰瑞德  第六季
So, Jared, season six.
什么
What?
你打败了路西法  丢了灵魂
You beat the devil, lost your soul,
然后又找了回来
and got it back again.
那么  接下来萨姆·温彻斯特会怎样
So tell us, what's next for Sam Winchester?
我真的不...
Look, I-I-I really don't --
回答的时候重复一下问题
Oh, and if you could include the question in your answer?
谢了
Thanks.
老弟  他们给咱们化妆
Dude, they put freakin' makeup on us!
那群混蛋
Those bastards!
-我想我知道怎么回事了  -怎么了
- Look, I think I know what this is. - Okay. What?
-是部电视剧  -还用你说
- It's a tv show. - You think?
我是说  这里  不管这里是哪
Yeah. I mean, here -- wherever "Here" is,
巴尔萨泽把我们塞进的这个灵异界
This -- this twilight zone Balthazar zapped us into.
不知怎的  我们的生活是部电视剧
For whatever reason, our life is a tv show.
-为什么  -我不知道
- Why? - I don't know.
说真的  怎么会有人喜欢看咱们的生活
No, seriously. Why? Why would anybody want to watch our lives?
根据刚采访我的那个人说
Well, I mean, according to that interviewer,
收视率挺低的
not very many people do.
我没说这事很合理
Look, I'm not saying it makes sense.
我只是说  我们掉到了某个次元
I'm just saying, we -- we landed in some dimension
在这里你是詹森·阿克斯
where you're Jensen Aackles,
我是什么杰瑞德·帕德里克
And I'm something called a "Jared Padalecki."
那你成波兰人了是么
So what, now you're Polish?
整件事都是扯淡
Is any of this making any sense to you?
至少我的宝贝也来了
Least my baby made it.
嘿
Hey.
喂  搞什么
Hey! What --
我感觉不舒服
I feel sick.
我要吐了
I'm gonna be sick.
我要回家
I want to go home.
这个地方简直让我毛骨悚然
I feel like this whole place is bad-touching me.
明白  我也是
Yeah, I know. Me too.
你觉得该怎么做  找小卡吗
So, what do you think? Cass?
找他最靠谱  如果他还活着的话
He's our best shot, if he's still alive.
亲爱的卡西迪奥
Dear Castiel,
也许你正忙着逃出天堂呢
who are... maybe running his ass away from heaven,
我们希望你能听到我们的祈祷
we pray that you have your ears on.
那么
So...
呼叫  呼叫
Breaker breaker...
小卡  是小卡  嘿  小卡
Cass? Cass! Hey, Cass!
噢  谢天谢地
Oh, thank god.
这是怎么回事
What is all this, huh?
巴尔萨泽对我们做了什么
W-w-what did Balthazar do to us?
为了让你俩不被维吉尔抓到
To keep you out of Virgil's reach,
他把你们送到了另一个现实里
he's cast you into an alternate reality,
一个和我们世界极其类似
a universe similar to ours in most respects
但某些方面又完全迥异的世界
yet dramatically different in others.
就像  就像比扎罗星球(DC漫画创造出的星球)那种  对吗
Like -- like Bizarro earth, right?
只不过这儿没有比扎罗超人
Except instead of having Bizarro superman,
有的却是一群蠢蛋
we get this clown factory.
是的  嗯
Yeah, well...
反正  现在没时间解释了
anyway, no time to explain.
-你是不是有钥匙  -是的
- Do you have the key? - Yeah.
不过这玩意儿是干嘛的
So, uh, what does this thing do, anyway?
是一个房间的钥匙
It opens a room.
房间里都有些啥
What's in the room?
巴尔萨泽从天堂偷出来的所有武器
Every weapon Balthazar stole from heaven.
他就这么拱手给我们了
He gave it to us?
为了保证钥匙安全  在我找到你们之前
To keep it safe until I could reach you.
有了那些武器  我就有机会恢复力量
With those weapons, I have a chance to rally my forces.
明白  真好
Oh. Okay, good. Yeah.
那这个电视剧啥的又是咋回事
So, now, uh, what's the deal with all this tv crap?
什么
Pardon?
问的好  帕德蕾丝克
Yeah. Amen, Padaleski.
-是"里克"  -啥
- Uh"Lecki.  - "What?
我很确定是帕德里克
Lecki. Pretty sure.
拜托
Man.
-难道又有新台词啊  -新的啥
- Did they put out new pages? - New what?
这是在开什么国际玩笑吗
I mean, is this some kind of cosmic joke?
如果真是的话  那就太冷了
Yeah, 'cause if it is, it's stupid,
-我们也没找到笑点  -没错
- and we don't get it. - Yeah.
你们俩没事吧
Are you guys okay?
给我拿来
Give me that.
这是
What is --
刚才那些全都是台词
These are words in a script.
-他根本不是小卡  -老哥  瞧瞧他
- This isn't Cass. - Dude, look at him.
你俩是想对台词  还是
You guys want to run lines, or...?
这小子叫米沙
His name's Misha.
米沙
Misha?
真是  太好了
Just...great.
米沙  詹森
Misha? Jensen?
这都是些啥鬼名字啊
What's up with the names around here?
你们俩小子
You guys!
还真是唬住我了
You really punked me!
我绝对要把这发到推特上
I'm totally gonna tweet this one.
你们好啊  米饭们
"Hola, Mishamigos.
J2骗得我好惨
"J-squared...got me good."
我真想把手伸进脑子里狂抓
I just want to dig my finger in my brain and scratch
直到我们回到堪萨斯州
until we're back in Kansas.
"真的开始觉得和其他人一样了"
"Really... starting to feel... like one of the guys."
J·阿克斯
"J. Ackles."
-那是假的我  -没错
- That's fake me! - Yeah.
这肯定是我的假房车
This must be fake mine.
老弟  我有一架直升机
Dude, I have a helicopter!
好吧  谁会放这么大的鱼缸在自己拖车里
All right, who puts a 300-gallon aquarium in their trailer?
显然就是詹森·阿克斯了
Apparently, Jensen Ackles.
好吧  我们来瞧瞧这家伙究竟是谁
All right, here we go. Let's see who this guy is.
看来他不是猎魔人
Well, he's not a hunter,
不过他扮演的角色是猎魔人
but he plays one on tv.
拜托
Come on.
瞧瞧这俩贱人  还一副模特范儿
Look at these male-modelin' sons of bitches.
这小表情做的  萨姆
Nice "Blue Steel," Sam.
很显然  那是我们的工作
Hey. Apparently, it's our job.
好了  听听这个
All right, uh, here goes.
网上说你来自德克萨斯州
Um...It says you're from Texas.
-真的  -是的
- Really? - Yeah.
还有就是
And, uh...
还说你演过一出肥皂剧
Says you were on a soap opera.
啥
What?
如果我没有得癌症
If I didn't have cancer,
如果我没有结婚  而且我还很有钱的话
and I wasn't married, and I had plenty of money...
你愿意跟我私奔吗
Would you -- would you want to run away with me?
钱
Money?
你觉得我真在乎钱吗  妮可
What, you think I really care about money, Nicole?
我在乎的是你的健康
I care that you're healthy.
我不是那种半途而废的人 艾瑞克
Well, I'm no quitter, Eric.
我  我
I-I --
我十分讨厌这里  小萨姆
Don't like this universe, Sammy.
我们必须离开这个世界
We need to get out of this universe.
没错  双手赞成
Yeah. No argument here.
不过我觉得小卡没有收到我们的呼叫
But I don't think our -- our prayers are reaching Cass.
确切地说是真正的小卡
Or the real Cass.
没错  我同意
Well, I agree.
我们绝对已经不在灵魂呼叫服务区了
I think we are definitely out of, uh, soul-phone range.
不过
But...
什么
What?
如果我们能颠倒巴尔萨泽的咒语
If we can reverse Balthazar's spell...
我留意了每一个步骤
I watched every move.
我们只需要找齐所有材料
We just, uh, get the ingredients, right,
再回到同一扇窗户前  然后
get back to that same window, and...
哪儿都不如自己的家好
...There's no place like home.
圣徒的脊椎
Backbone of a lesser Saint.
找到了
Got it.
是橡胶制品
It's rubber.
瞧瞧这个
Check this out.
瞧这个  是假的
Hey, look. It's fake.
全都是假的
It's all fake!
至少他俩开始说话了
Well, at least they're talking to each other.
这些垃圾对我们有屁用
What are we supposed to do with this crap?
这里的一切当然都是假的
'course everything is fake.
我们可是在片场啊
We're on a film set.
我们得回到真实世界去
We got to get back to the real world.
没错  你说到点上了
Yeah, now you're talking.
我们去找点儿真家伙
All right, we go round up the genuine articles,
再带回来继续那个咒语
bring 'em here for the spell.
怎么回事啊
What the hell is going on?
这家伙出什么毛病了
What is wrong with this thing?
-阿克斯先生  阿克斯先生  拜托  -迪恩
- Mr. Ackles! Mr. Ackles, please! - Uh, Dean?
上帝啊  阿克斯先生  求您停停
God, Mr. Ackles, please  stop!
-迪恩  它不是你的爱车  -请停停
- Dean, it's not the Impala. - Please stop!
停停
Stop.
-还用说么  -求您了
- You think? - Please!
这是个该死的道具
It's a frigging prop!
和那些假东西一样
Just like everything else.
谢谢你们
Oh, thank you.
谢谢  真是太感谢你们了
Thank you. Thank you so much for...
我们到底该怎么离开这该死的地方
How the hell are we supposed to get out of here?
你们俩想让我带你们去哪儿
You know whereabouts you want me to drop you off?
詹森
Jensen?
叫我  对
Me? Yes.
我只是跟着...
I -- I'll just tag along with, uh...
-杰瑞德  -杰瑞德
- Jared. - Jared. ...Jared here.
你俩什么时候开始说话的
Huh. Since when are you guys talking?
是啊  你也知道的  克林特
Yeah, uh, y-you know what, Clint, uh...
是克利夫
Uh, uh, Clif.
啊  对对  当然啊
Y-yeah. Yeah, of course.
克利夫  我知道
Clif. Obviously.
我们要回我家  然后做点...
Um, so, uh, I think we're gonna go back to my place a-and do some...
工作
Work.
演戏的事儿
Work on our acting.
-没错  -为了我们的角色
- Yeah. - For our characters.
-为这个剧  -对对
- For the show. - Yeah.
了解
All right.
话说回来  我们这是在哪儿呢
Where the hell are we, anyway?
(欢迎来到  温哥华)
老弟  我们都没在美国
Dude, we're not even in America.
真是低调的华丽啊  Jay-Z(美国嘻哈歌手)
Nice modest digs, Jay-z.
我肯定算得上是个中翘楚
I must be the star of this thing.
是的  没错
Yeah, right.
瞧瞧啊
Check it out.
我是个啥  德古拉吗
What am I, Dracula?
乔治·汉密尔顿版德古拉
George Hamilton Dracula.
这才对嘛
Now we're talking.
老弟  你后院里有头骆驼
Dude, you have a camel in your backyard.
那是羊驼  蠢货
It's an Alpaca, dumbass.
露比
Ruby?
露比  没错
"Ruby." Right.
还来这一套
That one never gets old.
今天的工作如何啊  亲爱的
How was work today, hon?
等等
Wait.
你跟露比
You and Ruby?
你觉着这有意思吗  詹森
Do you honestly think that's funny, Jensen?
对了
Right.
对了  你其实不是露比
Right. 'cause you're not Ruby.
你
You...
你怎么可能是她呢
I mean, how could you be?
你
You...
你当然就是  饰演露比的美女演员啦
Of course! You are the lovely actress who plays Ruby.
你出现在
And you are, uh, in...
杰瑞德家里
Jared's house,
是因为你们两个
Uh, because you two are
结婚了
married!
你娶了假露比
You married fake Ruby?
你们俩这是做什么呢
What are you doing?
工作
Work.
我就是想顺道过来  问个好
Yeah, just, uh, thought I'd pop in, say "Hey."
好啊
Hey.
还有  对对台词
Uh, and -- and -- and maybe run some lines. It's...
你从来就没来过我们家
You've never even been to our house.
今天看见你家后院有只羊驼
Well, now that I know there's an alpaca out back,
我下次一定还来
I'm definitely coming back.
羊驼是最环保的动物
Well, alpacas are the greenest animal.
是啊  是啊
Right. Right.
环保非常重要
That is so important.
我得去办事了
Well, there's that thing I have to get to.
啊对了  你有事
Oh, yeah. Of course, yeah. The thing.
国际海獭领养慈善晚宴
The International Otter Adoption Charity Dinner?
好吧
Okay, well...
你们终于和好了  我很高兴
Well, I'm glad you two are talking, anyway.
看来你过得挺滋润啊
Well, looks like you did all right.
我该去查查她叫什么名字
I should figure out her name.
"圣徒腕骨与圣物箱"
"Wrist bone of saint and holy reliquary.
"博物馆品质  出自瓦哈卡教区"
Museum-quality, from diocese in Oaxaca."
-看起来是真品  -成
- Looks legit. - All right.
拍卖所在墨西哥城
Auction house is in Mexico City.
我们后天能到
We could be there day after tomorrow.
装好之后拿东西走人  周末能回来
We, uh, case it, yank it, be back here by the end of the week.
或者直接买下来
Or we could just buy it.
什么  老弟  那东西十多万
What?! Dude, that thing's over a hundred thou--
你好  杰瑞德·帕德里克
Hello, Jared Padalecki.
是在海关见你朋友吗
Cubrir a su amigo en la aduana.
不是
No.
好的
Bueno.
加急快递  莫有问题
Triple rush. No problemo.
因为钱不是...
Because money is no ob...
这张刷爆了
This baby's maxed.
他们说货明天一早就送到机场
They said it should be at the airport first thing in the morning.
钱哪
Money, man.
有钱能使鬼推磨
There is nothing like it.
好了
All right.
沙发
Couch.
电视明星
TV star.
睡美容觉啦
Beauty rest.
珍  珍妮芙
Hi, uh, Gen-- Genevieve.
-阿珍  -阿珍
- Gen? - Gen.
阿珍  当然
Gen. Of course. Yeah.
那个
Um, so, h--
那个什么海赖
How was the...
的事怎么样
otter thing?
很好
It was good.
是吗
Yeah?
大家都很想你
Everybody missed you there.
那是
I bet.
我要问你件事
So -- so listen, I-I got to ask you a question.
你还记不记得
Do you remember, uh, uh,
前年  那些自然灾害
Year before last, all those disasters?
-自然灾害  -对
- Disasters? - Yeah.
地震频发
Yeah, yeah, the whole earthquake spike.
罗马9.2级地震
You know, the -- the 9.2 in Rome?
波士顿郊区8.5级
I mean, the -- the 8.5 outside Boston?
东西岸海啸连锁反应
The whole east/west tsunami chain?
是的
Yes.
我全都记得
I remember all of those
那是上一季剧情
from last season on your show.
不是  是  对对
No, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
我知道  我知道
I-I know. I know.
我说的就是这个  就是
That -- that's what I mean. That's what I was...
你是萨姆·温彻斯特演太久了
You have been Sam Winchester way too long.
抱歉打听一句
Sorry to pry, but, uh,
不过我们为什么要早上8点跑到这
why are we picking up packages at 8:00 a.m.
取一包还没办理报关手续的东西
that haven't cleared customs yet?
为了省时间
Just saving time.
好了  可算到手了
All right, here we go.
我们做的事违法吗
We're not doing anything illegal, are we?
-我们否认你会感觉好点不  -不会
- Would it make you feel better if we said no? - No.
怎么回事
Whoa. What?
今天就是累死也要12小时内拍完
We finish today in 12 hours if it kills us all.
让A机  B机就位  拍第12场
Get "A" And "B" Cam for scene 12.
怎么回事
What is this?
这么早就来排练了啊
Here for the first run-through, before anyone else?
敬业
Dedication.
能跟你谈谈吗
Uh, can I talk to you for a second?
我们需要清场
Um, we're gonna need the, uh, set cleared
保险起见  1小时左右
For -- safe side, an hour or so.
你要清场
You need it cleared.
对
Yeah.
对  我和
Yeah. Me and, um...
杰瑞德有些演员的事要做
Jared we're gonna do some actor stuff.
詹森
Jensen,
我们为你俩新颖的合作感到很欣慰
we're thrilled to see you collaborating so creatively.
热情之高令人为之一振
and your enthusiasm is refreshing.
迪恩·凯恩演《超人》的时候就是这样
Dean Cain was like that on "Lois,"
他是位真正的演员
And that man's a real actor.
我们会清场的
And we will clear this set
那得等拍好我们
exactly when we shoot the 2 3/8 pages
计划在这里拍的镜头之后
we are scheduled to shoot on this set.
你做好"演员的事"
So you do your "actor stuff"
我们做好"摄像的事"
and we'll do our "camera stuff" and, uh...
"急件"  里面装的什么
Ooh, "priority." What's in it?
我买了一个死人的尸骨
I bought parts of a dead person.
酷啊
Oh, cool.
坏消息
Uh, so, bad news.
貌似我们得演戏去了
Looks like we're gonna have to do a little acting.
什么
What?
《凶鬼恶灵》  第36场  第1次拍摄
"Supernatural" Scene 36, take 1.
标记
Marker!
开拍
Action!
巴尔萨泽才不是什么英雄
Balthazar is no hero.
他知道拉斐尔绝不会让他回去
But he knows Raphael will never take him back.
停
Cut!
《凶鬼恶灵》  第36场  第8次拍摄
"Supernatural" Scene 36, take 8.
标记
Marker!
开拍
Action!
巴尔萨泽才不是什么英雄
Balthazar is no hero.
他知道拉斐尔绝不会让他回去
But he knows Raphael will never take him back.
迪恩冷冷地说
Dean, grimly.
可是你却对此毫不介意
And yet, somehow you got no problem with it.
停
Cut!
开拍
Action.
那是因为
That's because...
那是因为我们别无选择
That's because we have no other choice.
别看镜头
Don't look at the camera.
什么
What?
看哪儿都行  别看镜头
Look anywhere but the camera.
那是因为我们别无选择
That's because we have no other choice!
停
Cut!
我的老天哪
For the love of...
开拍
Action.
停
Cut!
既然有钥匙
If there's a key,
那一定有把锁
then there must also be a lock.
停
Cut.
开拍
Action.
既然有钥匙
If there's a key...
就一定有把锁
then there has to be a lock.
我们找到那把锁
And when we find the lock,
就可以得到武器
we can get the weapons,
我们就可以得到那些武器
and then we can have the weapons.
还有锁  锁还在我们手里是吧
And the lock. We'll still have the lock, I imagine,
因为是我们开的锁  还有之前那把钥匙
because we've opened it, and, of course, the initial key.
我们得把这三样鬼玩意儿都找到
We need to get all three of that crap.
什么
What?
他说话就是这个调
That's how he talks. Oh.
我说这台词真的有必要吗
Do we really need all these lines?
我们不都演明白了嘛
I mean, I-I-I-I think we've covered it.
-是不是  -停
- Right? - Cut!
这是什么状况
What is happening?
什么状况
What's happening?!
神马状况啊
惨不忍睹的状况
An atrocity is happening.
看来他们不能演下去了
Seems like they should stop.
他们不能停
They can't stop.
都不准停
Nobody stops.
拍下的镜头有能用吗
Did we get anything we can use?
严格地说  我们拍下的都是
Well, uh, technically, we have them saying everything
他们说的七零八碎的台词
in bits and pieces.
这算是某种尝试吗
Could be sort of experimental?
无所谓啦
Whatever.
第六季
Season six.
谁写的
Who wrote this?
谁会说"倒数第二"啊
Nobody says "Penultimate!"
来把枪  放我嘴里
Gun, mouth.
就现在
Now.
下一场
Moving on!
谢天谢地
Thank god.
"依我拙见"
"I-m-h-o,
"J2昨晚肯定熬夜了"
'J' and 'J' had a late one last night."
见鬼
God damn it.
我们赚了这个
We earned this.
"咩哈哈笑使我了"
"R-o-t-f-l-m-a-o."
麻烦你给我讲清楚
Spell it out for me, please.
现在是什么级别的警戒
What is our terror-alert level here?
我不知道  瑟拉  橙色级别的吧
I don't know, Sera. Orange, maybe?
他们开始互相交谈了
They started talking to each other.
什么  不过那是件好事啊
What?! But that's a good thing.
对  我同意
Right. I thought so.
但是现在詹森住在杰瑞德的家里
But now Jensen's living at Jared's house.
-就这样  -还有  克利夫说他们从墨西哥
- That's it? - Plus, Clif says they're smuggling
-走私非法物品  -就这样 娘炮
- illegal stuff in from Mexico. - That's it, toto.
米沙在推特上说
Misha's celebrity tweet
是黑市倒卖器官什么的
says it's a black-market organ thing.
我打赌是毒品
I'm betting drugs.
反正就我看来
Anyway, as far as I can see,
他们已经失去了所有天分
I think they've lost any shred of talent they ever had.
肯定是毒品
Drugs.
可能我们搞错了
Maybe we did it wrong.
没有
No.
那个咒语非常正确
No, that -- that spell was perfect.
应该有效的
It should have worked.
如果不能起作用呢
What if it can't?
我一宿没睡  在网上查资料
Look, I was up all night, looking online.
这里没有发生过
There's no sign
天启一类的事件
that anything like the apocalypse happened here.
从未有过
Ever.
据我所知
And as far as I can tell,
怪物  鬼魂  恶魔
monsters, ghosts, demons --
都是假的
they're all pretend.
-那就是没人猎魔咯  -没有猎魔人
- So nobody's hunting them? - No hunters.
所以我们的咒语才没有效果  迪恩
Look, maybe that's why our spell didn't work, Dean, you know?
可能这里根本没有超自然力量
M-maybe here, there's no supernatural,
没有巫术
no magic.
没有恶魔  没有地狱
No demons, no hell,
没有天堂  没有上帝
no heaven, no -- no God?
差不多
Something like.
更好的是
Even better --
没有天使
no angels.
好吧  可能我们现在无法离开...
Okay, maybe we can't get out of, uh, you know,
这个"翻版地球"了
earth number two right now,
但是我们起码
but the least we can do
能离开加拿大这个鬼地方吧
is get the hell out of the Canadian part of it.
再听到冰球  我就要吐了
I hear one more conversation about hockey, I'm gonna puke.
等等
Wait a minute.
这边  这边  这边
This way, this way, this way.
不  不  不  应该是这边
No, no, no, no, no. It's this way.
是这边
It's this way!
不  迪恩  我真的认为  我们应该
No, Dean, look, I really -- I really think that we should --
迪恩
Dean!
你认为你跑得掉吗
You think you can run?
不
No!
抱歉老兄
Sorry, dude.
法力无效
Mojo-free zone.
这里用不了法术
No magic in the house.
所以你就是个普通的混蛋而已
Which makes you nothing but a dick.
我负责监督所有特技表演
You know, I oversee all the stunts,
还指导打斗戏份
coordinate all the fights.
太刺激了
That's exciting.
那也是你指导的吗
Is that one of yours, then?
大家过来
Guys!
不好  不好
Not good! Not good!
不  不  不
No, no, no, no!
住手  你们没搞明白
Stop! You don't understand!
不  不  不
No, no, no!
你死定了   维吉尔   维吉尔
You're dead, Virgil! Virgil!
我要把你的脖子扭断
I'm gonna break your friggin' neck! Hey!
鲍比  我只是想弄明白
I'm trying to understand, Bob.
瑟拉  我们自己也搞不懂
Well, uh, Sera, we don't really understand it ourselves,
但是  看上去好像杰瑞德和詹森
but, uh, it appears that Jared and Jensen
想把一个临时演员给揍死啊
were seen beating an extra to death.
我是吉姆  瑟拉  不是揍死
This is Jim here, Sera, and it wasn't all the way to death.
那人只是受了伤  顺便说下
Only partway, so that's a plus.
那人还能跑路呢
He could definitely still run.
我们会跟进这件事的
And we'll certainly follow up on that,
但是我觉得真正的问题是
but I think the real issue here, Sera,
这俩孩子好像长期
is that the boys appear to be
都迷迷糊糊的  跟嗑药了一样
on some kind of extended psychedelic acid trip.
是的  好吧
Well, uh, o-okay.
我飞过去和他们谈谈  可能会有帮助
Maybe it'd help if I -- I'll fly up and talk to them.
我不太确定杰瑞德和詹森
You know, I'm not sure Jared and Jensen...
知道她是谁  严格来说
know who she is, strictly speaking.
她还是一个新人  无意冒犯
She's, you know, new. No offense.
好吧
Right.
我觉着吧  眼下最需要的
Yeah, I think what we might need at this stage
就是能让克里普克亲自来一趟
is for Kripke to come up himself.
这剧是他创造的
He created the show.
他们会听他的话
They'll listen to him.
你让我情何以堪啊
How's that make me look?
这剧是我负责的
I'm supposed to be running this thing.
而且埃里克正宅在某地的小屋里
Besides, Eric is off in some cabin somewhere
筹写他的新剧呢
writing his next pilot.
-他卖了Octocobra  -是的
- He sold "Octocobra"? - Yes!
额滴那个神啊
Mother of god.
他们什么都买
They'll buy anything.
我搞不懂了  维吉尔跑出来了
I don't know. I mean, Virgil broke through.
可能他知道回去的办法
Maybe he's got a way to get back.
或者他在这里用不了法力
Or he has no juice here,
现在他和我们一样被困住了
and now he's stuck, like us.
不管怎样  我还没揍完呢
Yeah, either way, I want to finish kicking his ass.
晚安米沙
Good night, Misha.
晚安  小盆友
'night, little fella.
"你们是否有过这种感觉"
"Ever get that feeling...
"觉得有人潜藏在你的后座"
someone's in the backseat?"
"T_T"
Frowny face.
开车
Drive. Oh.
逮到你们了  有空吗
There you are, guys! You got a minute?
其实  我们在找
Actually, we're -- we're looking for,
你们想杀死的那个临时演员
Uh -- for that extra you tried to kill?
为钱吗
So, is it money?
如果我们再给你们加点钱
Is this the kind of act that goes away
你们就能消停了是吗
if we can scare up some coverage on a raise?
加薪
More money?
你付给这俩家伙的钱已经够多了
You already pay these two jokers enough as it is. Yeah.
因为我觉得吧  过了这么些年了
'cause I'd like to think that over these years,
我们日益亲密
we've grown closer.
你们不当我是鲍比导演
That you don't think of me as "Director bob"
也不是监制人鲍比·辛格
or "Executive producer Bob Singer,"
而是鲍比叔叔
but as "Uncle Bob."
等等  你开玩笑吧
Wait, you're kidding.
这剧里的角色  鲍比·辛格
So, the character in the show, Bobby Singer --
哪个猪头会给角色取个和自己一样的名字
What kind of douchebag names a character after himself?
这不对
Oh, that's not right.
好吧  我们重新开始
Okay, guys, let's begin again.
-好的  -好的
- Yeah. - Yeah.
我觉得维吉尔没拿到那把钥匙
You know, I don't think Virgil would have shagged out of here
是不会离开这里的
without getting his mitts on that key. Yeah.
没错  我同意
Yeah, I agree.
伙计们
Guys...
你们不能嗑完药来工作啊
You can't come to work on poppers
还从墨西哥走私肾脏入国
and smuggle kidneys in from Mexico
还随便乱改台词
and make up your own lines as you go!
你们不能随便乱改台词
You cannot make up your own lines!
上帝啊  你们的演艺事业怎么办啊
Good god, what about your careers?
去他娘的演艺事业  鲍比
You know what? Screw our careers, Bob.
什么
What?!
你听到我弟弟的话了
You heard my brother.
对  我说的是"弟弟"
That's right, I said "brother."
鲍比  你知道么
'cause you know what, Bob?
我们不是演员
We're not actors.
我们是猎魔人
We're hunters.
我们是温家人
We're the Winchesters.
以前是  现在是  以后也是
Always have been, and always will be.
我们的世界里  没人知道我们是谁
And where we're from, people don't know who we are.
但是跟你说
But you know what?
在那个世界  我们至关重要
We mattered in that world.
事实上  我们还偶尔救救人命
In fact, we even saved a son of a bitch once or twice.
对  好吧  这里也许有一些粉丝
And yeah, okay, here, maybe there's some -- some fans
很在乎这些个垃圾
who give a crap about this nonsense.
我可不会称之为垃圾
I wouldn't call it nonsense.
但是  鲍比·辛格
But, Bob Singer --
如果这是你的名字
If that even is your name --
告诉我
tell me this --
这意味着什么
what does it all mean?
好的  很好啊
Okay. This is good.
我是说  我们都有神经质的时候
I mean, we've all had our psychotic breaks, right?
我完全理解
I can work with this.
迪恩
Dean.
维吉尔  他把钥匙拿走了
Virgil -- I think he has the key.
我们辞演
We quit.
好的  好的  别动气  别动气
Okay, okay, okay. Easy, easy.
你是怎么做到的
How do you do it?
别
please.
生活在这种鸟不拉屎又脏又破的地方
Live in this grubby, shabby desert?
这里跟你们一样  一无是处
Nothing greater than yourselves.
死后不过是一小撮尘土
Nothing but dirt when you die.
你说什么
What? Aah!
没有超能力  没有魔法
No power, no magic.
我根本  我根本不知道你在说什么
I'm so-- I'm not following you at all.
这里什么魔法都不存在
There's no magic in your universe!
抱歉
I'm sorry!
求你
Please!
-只有一袋绳子和滑轮  -你说什么
- Nothing but a bag of strings and pulleys. - What?!
你该感激接下来我对你做的事
You should thank me for what I'm about to do.
为什么  你究竟要对我做什么
Why? What are you about to do?
我要做一个很重要的召唤
I need to make an important call.
我向上帝祈求能够成功
I pray to god that it even goes through.
我也沦落到如此了
This is what I've been reduced to.
拉斐尔
Raphael.
也许我们可以黑入警察的调度系统
Maybe if we get inside the police dispatch system.
给维吉尔弄一张全国通缉令
Put out an A.P.B. On Virgil.
也许有用  如果他还这样招摇过市的话
Might work, if he stays obvious.
我们的时间不多了
It's not like we have a lot of time.
我的天  我的天
Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
怎么了
What?
米沙  他被人刺死了
Misha! He's been stabbed to death!
-在哪里  -在哪里
- Where? - Where?
你们有良心没啊
Where?!
警告  禁止入内
Caution do not enter.
没错  是拉斐尔  跟忍者神龟一名字
Yeah, yeah, Raphael. Like the ninja turtle.
他当时在召唤一个来自天堂的  名叫拉斐尔的人
He was calling someone name of Raphael, up in heaven.
没错  没错  就是那样
Yeah, yeah. That's right.
那个可怕的男人杀了这个大哭大叫的帅哥
The -- the scary man killed the attractive crying man,
然后他就开始祷告
and then he started to pray.
最奇怪的是
And the strange part --
过了不久
after a while,
我发誓听到有个声音回应他
I s-swear I heard this voice, answering.
那它说了什么
What did it say?
听上去就是一派胡言
Well, it didn't make any sense.
说来听听
Try us.
那个声音说
The voice said,
"明天维吉尔即将回去"
"For Virgil to return tomorrow,
"从来时的那个地方”
"at the place where he crossed over,
"和来时的那个时间"
"at the time of the crossing.
"拉斐尔将会透过那个窗户”
"And Raphael would reach through the window
"并带他和那把钥匙回去"
and take him and the key home."
好的
Uh, okay.
谢谢
Hey, thank you.
迪恩  如果维吉尔带着那把钥匙回去
Dean, if Virgil gets back with that key,
小卡就死定了  我们的世界也完蛋了
Cass is dead, and our world is toast.
那我们就阻止他
Well, then we stop him.
一个没了翅膀的天使还能有多厉害呢
I mean, how bad can an angel with no wings be?
我想看看那支半压动式步枪
I'd like to see that pump-action tactical,
口径12毫米
12-gauge.
好的
You bet.
眼光不错
Nice choice.
先生  你对军械真是了如指掌
You really know your ordnance, mister.
我是天堂的武器管理者
I am the weapons keeper of heaven.
你说什么
Excuse me?
说的我工作
It's my job.
如果我们阻止了维吉尔  拿到钥匙
You know that if we drop Virgil, get the key,
那也许就得长住在这了
then this might be it.
我们很可能就困死在这了
We might be stuck here.
不  我们会找到回去的方法
No, we'll figure out a way back.
是啊  尽管回不去对你也没坏处
Yeah, you wouldn't be that broken up if we didn't, though.
什么
What?
别傻了
Don't be stupid.
我只是想说
Well, I'm just saying.
下面没有地狱  上面没有天堂
No hell below us, above us only sky.
迪恩  我们的朋友都不在这里
Dean, our friends are back there.
是啊  可这里  你有个完美的生活
Yeah, but here, you got a pretty good life.
我是说  从你6个月大起  那个地方就
I mean, back home, the hits have been coming
一直没消停过
since you were 6 months old.
你得承认  当个有钱人
You got to admit, being a-a bazillionare,
还跟露比结了婚  一切完美
married to Ruby, the whole package.
这无可厚非
It's no contest.
知道吗  你说对了
No, you know, you were right.
这里的生活确实很不一样
We just don't mean the same thing here.
我是说  我们在这里都不是兄弟关系了
I mean, we're not even brothers here, man.
好  那我们就开始疯狂的回家行动吧
All right, then. Let's get our crazy show back home.
鲍比  兄弟  究竟怎么了
Bob, dude. What the hell, right?
-埃里克  谢谢你能来  -别这么说
- Eric. Thanks for coming. - Of course.
我知道你很忙
I know you're busy.
这对我们来说意义很大  还可以请你帮忙
It means a lot that we can still, you know, call on you.
是的  没错  米沙  对吗
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Misha, right?
我知道  我知道  这可真是个悲剧
Oh, I know, I know. It's just awful!
这绝对  绝对是悲剧
It's totally, totally awful. Yeah.
可也让我们上了报纸头条   你看了吗
It got us the front page of variety, though. Did you see that?
-头条  真的吗  -没错  没错
- Front page? Really? - Yeah, yeah.
但还是个悲剧
But tragic.
是的  是悲剧  我也这么认为
Yeah, tragic. That's what I was gonna say.
你的"Octocobra"如何了
How's "Octocobra"?
我觉得我找到了突破口
Oh, I think I really had a breakthrough.
午饭的时候我会跟你好好谈谈
I'll tell you all about it over lunch, though.
我都等不及了
I can't wait.
是啊
Yeah.
好的  那我就先去他们的拖车里
Okay, so I am just gonna bust in their trailer,
好好教训他俩一顿  然后再处理那些乱七...
guns blazing, and then take care of this whole mess and --
怎么了
What?
那个人  他就是那个临时演员
That guy. I think that's the extra!
太好了
Oh, fantastic.
我们可以先把他扼杀在摇篮里
We can nip this bud right out of the gate.
你好  临时演员
Hey, extra!
过来这边
Over here!
枪  他手里有枪
Gun! He's got a gun!
不要啊
Noooooo!
今天应该没有枪战的戏  不是吗
I don't think we have gunfire on the call sheet today, hmm?
这呢
Hey!
迪恩  我拿到了
Dean, got it!
拉斐尔来了  快跑
Raphael. Run!
你们两个...
You two...
每次都这么走运
have the strangest luck.
拉斐尔
Raphael?
这肉身不错
Nice meatsuit.
老兄看起来是个女人
Dude looks like a lady.
给我钥匙
The key.
那只是奥尔巴尼车站一个储物柜的钥匙
And that will open you a locker at the albany bus station.
是吗
Really.
我得找个合适的诱饵  不然怎么让你相信呢
You see, I needed a modest decoy to make it more convincing.
给我武器
Give me the weapons.
抱歉  亲爱的  它们不见了
Sorry, darling. They're gone.
你说什么
What?!
我说  太迟了
I said, too bloody late.
知道吗  它们藏得太隐蔽了
You see, they were so well-hidden
所以我需要点时间去找它们
that I needed time to find them.
所以我就让这两个小猴子
So, I volunteered these two marmosets
去和维吉尔玩了场抛接游戏
for a game of fetch with Virgil.
你们两个真是相当的好用
You two were such an adequate stick.
谢谢你们俩了
Thank you. Thank you, boys.
这是你犯的最后一个错误了
You've made your last mistake.
我的招数可不仅仅如此
Oh, I've got a few more up my sleeve,
亲爱的
Honey.
拉斐尔  离他远点
Step away from him, Raphael.
我拿到了武器  现在它们的力量都属于我
I have the weapons now. Their power is with me.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
不想今晚死的话  就快离开
If you don't want to die tonight, back off.
那么  小卡
Well, Cass...
...现在你得到了武器  可千万别玩火自焚
...Now that you have your sword, try not to die by it.
小卡  究竟怎么回事
Cass, what the hell?
等等  你也有份参与
Wait, you were in on this,
用我们来分散敌人注意力
using us as a diversion?
是巴尔萨泽的计划
It was Balthazar's plan.
我也会这么做的
I would have done the same thing.
小卡  这听着可不舒服
That's not comforting, Cass.
你们究竟要怎样才明白
When will I be able to make you understand?
如果我输给了拉斐尔  我们就都完了
If I lose against Raphael, we all lose.
都得完蛋
Everything.
是的  小卡   我们清楚这点
Yeah, Cass. We know the stakes.
问题是你竟然瞒着我们
That's about all you've told us!
对此我感到非常抱歉
I'm sorry about all this.
可以的时候我会解释的
I'll explain when I can.
该死的小翅膀
Friggin' angels.
实体的
Solid.
这是真的
It's real.
很好
Nice.
是啊
Yeah.
真实的  霉味十足的  摇摇欲坠的可爱的家
Yeah, real, moldy, termite-eaten home sweet home.
还有一大堆恨不得把我们活剥的东西
Chock full of crap that want to skin you.
还有
Oh, and, uh,
我们又成了穷鬼
We're broke again.
是啊
Yeah.
但是
But, hey...
至少我们在说话
At least we're talking.